Hello Hello friends, welcome to our
YouTube channel One World. Friends, in today's
video, I will tell you
about Aditya Birla Sun Life Term Insurance.
Friends, before proceeding further in the video,
I would like to request you that if
you have not yet subscribed to this channel, then you
must subscribe to it.
And if you like this video, then
definitely share it. So friends, let's clear this video.
Friends, Aditya
Birla Sun Life Insurance Company Limited is
a leading insurance provider
company in India. This company is a joint venture between Aditya Birla Group
and Sant-Mahatma Life Insurance Services
and Madison, which is a Canadian
returned Jayson.
This company
started its operations in India in January 2001. Friends, Aditya Birla Sun
Life Insurance Company,
along with term insurance, provides different types of insurance
products in the Indian market,
which fulfill the different types of customer
needs. Friends, Aditya
Birla Sun Life Insurance Company
provides three types of Aditya Birla Sun Life Term Insurance plans.
First
Aditya Birla Sun Life's term insurance plan
allows the policyholder to choose from eight career options.
It has been designed keeping in mind the needs of the policyholder's family members. This ensures that
if the policyholder dies, there is no
disruption in the family's lifestyle. In the expansion plan,
policyholders can add several additional coverages to enhance their coverage, thereby further enhancing the
benefits received from this term insurance. The
second is the Aditya Birla Sun Life Prodigious
Shoulder Term Insurance Plan.
Aditya Birla Sun Life's BTC and
Vitamin Liner plan assures the policyholder of 10 different
types of coverage.
This term insurance plan
gives the policyholder the option to choose from a single or multiple life insurance coverage. The death benefit
paid to a family member through this policy can be a
death benefit, a Mustafa Minister, or a
combination of both. This can be
selected by the policyholder at the time of purchasing the policy.
Along with providing life insurance coverage, this plan also
provides the option of return of premium. The
policy premium paid by the policy holder is
returned at the end of the policy term.
Friends, every third of this plan has Aditya Birla Sun Life Saral Jeevan
Bima Yojana. Friends, Aditya
Birla Sun Life Saral Jeevan Bima Yojana is another
simple insurance plan
which provides a lump sum amount as death benefit to the family members on the death of the policy holder
so that the
financial needs of the family can be met.
Along with this, you can also enhance
your insurance coverage by adding extra riders to it.
These
riders can be added simultaneously by looking at it.
This plan also gives the option of one payment of premium
i.e. 110 payments or
another specific payment till the end of the term
or premium payment for the entire plan.
Friends, let's talk about Aditya Birla
Sun Life Term Insurance.
Aditya Birla Sun Life Term
Insurance offers many types of benefits and
offers you many benefits.  In this, you get
fancy Allah security belt
options for the family at a low cost, like coverage and riders and
tax benefits etc.
Friends, now I will tell you about it in
detail. Friends, in case of
death of the policyholder,
in that situation, this security is provided to him and his family.
Through this term insurance plan, friends, the
insured person normally
receives a sum assured in the form of Amrit Phal (Amrit Phal). This sum assured can be used to meet the family
's household expenses, loans and other
liabilities.
Friends, in the 1958 insurance policy,
you can choose the sum assured option.
If the policyholder dies, then the
sum assured is paid to the family in
a book. This can be provided as a one-time payment or as a four-
monthly income or as a combination of both.
This is very helpful in meeting the regular expenses of the family and
other individuals.
Friends, this term
insurance policy provides the policyholder with a high income
at a low premium cost.  It provides coverage.
If you buy this term insurance
policy at a young age, then
you have to pay the premium as well.
Therefore, it is necessary that you and we try to buy this
term insurance policy as soon as possible at a young
age.
You can add multiple riders in it.
Through this, you can increase the coverage of your policy
further and double your benefit.
Friends,
by making a clear payment, you
can add additional riders to your account. These
riders include accidental death riders,
disability riders, team shot rider,
hospitalization rider, surgical battery etc.
Friends, you
also get tax benefit in this.
Income tax and 19611 points on the premium paid are applicable
and you are eligible for tax deduction up to a maximum of Rs. 1.5 lakh as per section 80C.
Apart from this,
Akhilesh Birla To fortune received by a normal person on the death of the policyholder
is for further exemption as per section 80C of Income Tax and 9061. Friends, there are
many types of benefits to increase the insurance and constipation.
You can increase your benefit by
adding these riders to your account through the same.
Now let me
tell you about the non-riders.
Friends, the first benefit is
accidental death and disability. Idea: Friends,
through accidental death and rider,
if you and the appointed person die during this period, then
apart from the normal death life, you are
also provided with accidental death benefit and rider
payment. If the person becomes disabled
in an accident, then
he is given a lump sum amount i.e. payment on the
demand of the incident.
Therefore, through this RS,
you
can add extra benefits to your policy. Friends, and the
second item is surgical and disability rider.
Friends, the surgical care rider provides a lump sum payment to the
insured in case of admission to any hospital in India
and undergoing a surgical procedure,
through which he can
easily cover the expenses incurred on his body.
This amount can be from ₹3000 to  The
third is the Critical Illness Rider.
In the Critical Illness Rider, the insured is provided a
covered benefit of up to 800% of the sum insured. The
fourth is the Hospital Line and Hospital
Hq Quid. If the insured is
admitted to the hospital for at least 24 hours, he or she is paid a deductible amount as an expense.
ICU health benefits are also provided in this plan.
This can range from ₹100 to ₹
6000. The fifth
is the Remembrance Discount. Under this
plan, if the insured becomes
disabled in an accident,
he or she is given a further exemption in paying the premium, that is,
all his or her premiums are
waived. In the Aditya Birla Sun
Life Term Insurance Plan,
death cover is not provided in certain cases. Let
me tell you about it. If you are a fiancée and are involved in
dangerous sports or other
activities such as hunting, rough
mountaineering, racing, or even horse racing, you can also get a discount.  Partial, complete, or partial disability due to
participation in bungee jumping etc. is
not included in this policy. It also covers swank coat or
suicide or attempted suicide.
Disability, injury, or death due to service in the Army, Air Force, Navy, or Paramilitary Forces is
excluded from this policy. In case of loss due to
strike,
industrial dispute, war,
civil disobedience, terrorism in
media, chemical and fodder
contamination, or nuclear reaction,
etc., the
insured is not provided with benefits. You can buy
Aditya Birla Sun Life Term Insurance
Plan online or offline. If you want to take this policy online, you will have to visit the
company's official website and provide the required documents. After this, you can take the policy online by making the payment. If you want to take this policy through online mode, then you will have to go to the company's official website
and
provide the required documents. After this,
you can take the policy online by making the payment.
Friends, if you
want to take this policy through online mode, then you will have to go
through an entry broker for this.  You will have to apply for this, for this
you may have to take some actions
also, so friends, in today's
video we learned what is Aditya Birla Sunlife
and Term Insurance and
I have told you about it in more detail
in this video, if
you like this video then do share it with your friends
and tell us by commenting in the comment box
how you liked this video, we will
meet in the next video with some other topic, till then
thank you
[Music] It is done
and sing it again
[Music]